Inventory of the Ginetta Sagan papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- Vietnam research materials, 1976-1996
  - V65. Jacqueline Desbarats and Karl Jackson articles, 1984 (Box-folder 302: 29)
  - V66. Vietnam maps, 1980s (Box-folder 302: 30)
  - V67. Admission of Vietnam to the United Nations, 1977 (Box-folder 303: 1)
  - V68. "Vietnamese Perspectives on International Security," by Carlyle Thayer, 1989 (Box-folder 303: 2)
  - V69. List of Catholic priests detained in concentration camps, 1982 July (Box-folder 303: 3)
  - V70. Red Cross, 1983 (Box-folder 303: 4)
  - V71. "The Official Policy of Repression in the Socialist Republic of Vietnam," by Stephen Denney, 1982 March (Box-folder 303: 5)
  - V72. Vietnam Reconsidered conference, 1983 (Box-folder 303: 6)
  - V73. Boat People, 1979 (Box-folder 303: 7)
  - V74. Yale Southeast Asia Studies, 1984 (Box-folder 303: 8)
  - V75. Filing Vietnam reports at the United Nations, 1983 (Box-folder 303: 9)
  - V76. Protestants, 1984 (Box-folder 303: 10)
  - V77. Vietnam reports, 1990, undated (Box-folder 303: 11)
  - V78. Vietnam bibliography on computer disk, 1990 March 8 (Box-folder 303: 12)
  - V79. Vietnam offer of help, undated (Box-folder 303: 13)
  - V80. Grafton Christian Church and Church World Service, 1983-1985 (Box-folder 303: 14)
  - V81. New economic zones, 1977 (Box-folder 303: 15)
  - V82. Doan Phan Tri prisoner questionnaire, 1983 (Box-folder 303: 16)
  - V83. Thich nu Tri Hai, Buddhist nun, 1984 (Box-folder 303: 17)
  - V84. "General Giap's Victory," Wall Street Journal, 1984 May 7 (Box-folder 303: 18)
  - V85. Reviews of Violation of Human Rights report, 1984 (Box-folder 303: 19)
  - V86. Aurora press releases on Vietnam, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 303: 20)
  - V87. Humanitas, 1983-1986 (Box-folder 303: 21)
  - V88. Ginetta's notes on Vietnam, undated (Box-folder 303: 22)
  - V89. Memo by GS to AIUSA Board of Directors, 1985 February 12 (Box-folder 303: 23)
  - V90. Human rights in the Socialist Republic of Vietnam, Aurora Foundation press release, 1983 December 11 (Box-folder 303: 24)
  - V91. "Vietnam: Where Are the Crowds?" San Francisco Examiner, 1984 January 3 (Box-folder 303: 25)
  - V92. "Repression in Vietnam: One Woman Attempts to 'Awaken' the US," Public Research Syndicated, 1983 (Box-folder 303: 26)
  - V93. Notes on Vietnam by GS, undated (Box-folder 303: 27)
  - V94. Protestants, 1984-1987 (Box-folder 303: 28)
  - V95. French reports on Vietnam, undated (Box-folder 303: 29)
  - V96. Stephen Denney on Buddhism, 1979-1996 (Box-folder 304: 1)
  - V97. Reeducation camp reports, 1981 (Box-folder 304: 2)
  - V98. Clippings, collected articles and notes by GS, 1980-1983 (Box-folder 304: 3)
  - V99. Vietnam address lists, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 304: 4)
  - V100. Address lists, 1985-1987 (Box-folder 304: 5)
  - V101. GS's comments on House Resolution 8726, 1987 (Box-folder 304: 6)
  - V102. Stephen Denney correspondence, 1981 (Box-folder 304: 7)
  - V103. Vietnam correspondence, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 304: 8)
  - V104. Katie Jones, Tom Jones, and Clair Schlumberger correspondence, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 305: 1)
  - V105. Regis Debray correspondence, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 305: 2)
  - V106. Journalist correspondence, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 305: 3)
  - V107. Vietnam correspondence, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 305: 4)
  - V108. Theodore Pruett correspondence, 1984 (Box-folder 305: 5)
  - V109. Philip Marcus correspondence, 1982-1984 (Box-folder 305: 6)
  - V110. Smith Richardson Foundation, 1984 (Box-folder 305: 7)
  - V111. Michael Williams correspondence, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 305: 8)
  - V112. GS notes, 1979-1987 (Box-folder 305: 9)
  - V113. Nguyen Hong Thanh, 1984 (Box-folder 305: 10)
  - V114. American Friends Service Committee, 1978-1981 (Box-folder 305: 11)
  - V115. Vietnam correspondence and notes, 1984 and undated (Box-folder 305: 12)
  - V116. Address lists, 1990 (Box-folder 305: 13)
  - V117. Violations report correspondence, 1990 (Box-folder 305: 14)
  - V118. Vietnam correspondence, 1980, 1988 (Box-folder 305: 15)
  - V119. Vietnam correspondence and notes, 1980-1990 (Box-folder 305: 16)
  - V120. Vietnam research materials, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 305: 17)
  - V121. Vietnam correspondence, 1980-1990 (Box-folder 306: 1)
  - V122. Vietnam notes and lists, 1981-1987 and undated (Box-folder 306: 2)
  - V123. Vietnam correspondence, 1987-1991 (Box-folder 306: 3)
  - V126. Index to Vietnam notes, after 1985 (Box-folder 306: 4)
  - V127. Religion in Vietnam, undated (Box-folder 306: 5)
  - V128. Index to Vietnam notes, after 1985 (Box-folder 306: 6)
  - V129. Original reeducation chapter, after 1987 (Box-folder 306: 7)
  - V130. Drafts on reeducation camps, 1988 May 5 (Box-folder 306: 8)
  - V131. Vietnam cases-active, 1982-1986 (Box-folder 306: 9)
  - Footnotes and bibliography for 1989 Vietnam report (Box-folder 306: 10)
  - Clippings and research materials for Vietnam report, 1973-1985 (Box-folder 306: 11)
  - V132. Vietnam bibliographies, 1989 (Box-folder 307: 1)
  - V133. Correspondence and research materials relating to Vietnam report, 1982-1990 (Box-folder 307: 2)
  - Reports and research materials on Vietnam, 1980s (Box-folder 307: 3-5)
  - V139. Vietnam research materials, 1980s (Box-folder 308: 1)
  - Notes by GS on Vietnam, 1980s (Box-folder 308: 2-4)
  - Research materials on reeducation camps, 1984-1987 (Box-folder 308: 5)
    Includes prisoner lists
  - Research materials on Vietnam, 1986 (Box-folder 308: 6)
    Includes bibliography by GS
  - V142. Indochina Chronology, 1986-1989 (Box-folder 309: 1)
  - V143. Reader's Digest proposal, 1990 (Box-folder 309: 2)
  - V144. Olin Foundation Vietnam proposal, 1985-1990 (Box-folder 309: 3)
  - V145. Eldridge Foundation, 1985-1990 (Box-folder 309: 4)
  - V146. Institute for Educational Affairs, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 309: 5)
  - V147. MacArthur Foundation proposal, 1986 (Box-folder 309: 6)
  - V148. Anchorage Foundation proposal, 1989-1991 (Box-folder 309: 7)
  - V149. Pike, Douglas, 2002 (Box-folder 309: 8)
  - V150. Amnesty International press release on Vietnam, 1983 April 20 (Box-folder 309: 9)
  - V151. Paris Agreements, circa 198 (Box-folder 309: 10)
  - V152. Asia Watch reports, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 309: 11)
  - V153. Amnesty International press releases on Vietnam, 1990 (Box-folder 309: 12)
  - V154. Van Hoi Moi, 1982 (Box-folder 309: 13)
  - V155. Radio broadcast report from Vietnam, 1987 June 29 (Box-folder 309: 14)
  - V156. California Senate Joint Resolution on Vietnamese political prisoners, 1988 January 22 (Box-folder 309: 15)
  - V157. Indochina Issues, 1981-1989 (Box-folder 309: 16)
  - V158. Institute for Democracy in Vietnam, 1988 (Box-folder 309: 17)
  - V159. Nguyen Van Canh, 1986 May (Box-folder 309: 18)
  - V160. Aurora Foundation drafts and reports, 1980s (Box-folder 310: 1)
  - V161. Persecution of writers and journalists in Vietnam, 1988 May 10 (Box-folder 310: 2)
  - V162. Vietnam Commentary, 1988 (Box-folder 310: 3)
  - V163. The Voice of Indochina, 1986 (Box-folder 310: 4)
  - V164. Refugee reports, 1989 (Box-folder 310: 5)
  - V165. UN report on Indochina, undated (Box-folder 310: 6)
  - V166. Vietnam veterans clippings, 1990 (Box-folder 310: 7)
  - V167. Association of Vietnamese Catholics in Germany, 1986 (Box-folder 310: 8)
  - V168. Matchbox, 1978 (Box-folder 310: 9)
  - V169. Vietnam Echos, 1989 October (Box-folder 310: 10)
  - V170. Indochina Journal, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 310: 11)
  - V171. Vietnam clippings, 1971-1991 (Box-folder 310: 12)
  - V172. Vietnam reports by Stephen Young, 1979 (Box-folder 310: 13)
  - V173. Families of Vietnamese Political Prisoners Association, 1988-1990 (Box-folder 311: 1)
  - V174. Vietnam democracy, 1995 November (Box-folder 311: 2)
  - V175. Nguyen Chi Thien, 1989-1991 (Box-folder 311: 3)
  - V176. "Prisoners of Conscience," by Ginetta Sagan, after 1979 (Box-folder 311: 4)
  - V177. Aurora Foundation press releases on Vietnam, 1989 (Box-folder 311: 5)
  - V178. Wibault, Henri, 1990 (Box-folder 311: 6)
  - V179. Vietnam correspondence, 1977-1990 (Box-folder 311: 7)
  - V180. Unified Buddhist Church, 1978-1995 (Box-folder 311: 8)
  - V181. Tran Van Tuyen, after 1976 (Box-folder 311: 9)
  - V182. Nguyen Dan Que, 1990-1992 (Box-folder 311: 10)
  - V183. Lucien Trong writings, 1980 (Box-folder 311: 11)
  - V184. Vietnam clippings, 1987-1991 (Box-folder 311: 12)
  - V185. Vietnam notes, undated (Box-folder 311: 13)
  - V186. Vietnam clippings, circa 1970 (Box-folder 311: 14)
  - V187. Petition by former prisoners in Vietnam submitted to Amnesty International, circa 1989 (Box-folder 311: 15)
  - V188. Vietnam research materials in French, 1989 (Box-folder 311: 16)
  - V189. Vietnamese refugees in Thailand, 1981 (Box-folder 311: 17)
  - V190. Stephen Denney correspondence, 1982 March 23 (Box-folder 311: 18)
  - V191. 60 Minutes transcript on Vietnam, 1982 June 13 (Box-folder 311: 19)
  - Miscellaneous research materials on Vietnam, 1980s-1990s (Box 312)
- Subject files, 1971-2004
  Includes biographical and research files assembled by Sim Smiley
  - Afghanistan, 1989-1999 (Box-folder 313: 1)
  - Algeria, 1998 (Box-folder 313: 2)
  - Amnesty International, 1978-2003
    - Concerts, 1985-1990 (Box-folder 313: 3)
    - Group 19, 1978-2003 (Box-folder 313: 4)
    - Italy, 1991-1992 (Box-folder 313: 5)
    - Urgent Action, 1982-1996 (Box-folder 313: 6)
  - Arriaga, Alex, 1996-2002 (Box-folder 313: 7)
  - Awards, 1980-1996 (Box-folder 313: 8)
  - Awards (cont'd.), 1980-1996 (Box-folder 314: 1)
  - Baez, Joan, 1971-2003 (Box-folder 314: 2)
    Includes photograph
  - Bambini di Guerra, 1995-1999 (Box-folder 314: 3)
  - Banfi, Arialdo, 1977-1997 (Box-folder 314: 4)
  - Bernstein, Leonard, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 314: 5)
  - Brommer, Penny, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 314: 6)
    Contains notes by Brommer for a book on GS
  - Brown, Irving, 1989 (Box-folder 314: 7)
  - Brusson, 1989-1997 (Box-folder 314: 8)
    Includes photographs of GS and Joan Baez in Brusson
  - Brzezinski, Zbigniew, 1987, 1990 (Box-folder 314: 9)
  - Bush, G.W., 1999 November 16 (Box-folder 315: 1)
  - Cambodia, 1982-1997 (Box-folder 315: 2)
  - Campaign for Abolition of Torture, 1975-1983 (Box-folder 315: 3)
  - Carter, Jimmy, 1975-2003 (Box-folder 315: 4)
  - Cartoons, undated (Box-folder 315: 5)
    Includes some by Baez
  - Children, 1988-1992 (Box-folder 315: 6)
  - Chile, 1974-1989 (Box-folder 315: 7)
  - Concentration camps, 1945-1996 (Box-folder 315: 8)
  - Congress, 1979-1991 (Box-folder 315: 9)
  - Czechoslovakia, 1981-1988 (Box-folder 315: 10)
  - Cooking (recipes), 1960s-1990s (Box-folder 315: 11)
  - Cuba, 1993 (Box-folder 315: 12)
  - Damesyn, Andrea, 1983-2001 (Box-folder 315: 13)
  - D'Andrea, Shirley, 1995-1999 (Box-folder 315: 14)
  - Dorman, Robin, 1989-1993 (Box-folder 315: 15)
  - FBI, 1974 April 4 (Box-folder 315: 16)
    On Patricia Hearst
  - Forbidden Film, 1984 (Box-folder 315: 17)
  - Fundraising, 1973-2001 (Box-folder 315: 18)
  - Geyelin, Phil, 1967-2000 (Box-folder 315: 19)
  - Gluzman, Semyon, 1986-1988 (Box-folder 316: 1)
  - Grande Ufficiale, 1996 (Box-folder 316: 2)
  - Greece, 1971-1985 (Box-folder 316: 3-4)
  - Ginetta Sagan Fund, 1995-2002 (Box-folder 316: 5-12)
  - Gibbs, John, 1977-1978 (Box-folder 317: 1)
  - Guatemala, 1980 February 11 (Box-folder 317: 2)
  - Harkins, K., 1986-1999 (Box-folder 317: 3)
  - Healey, Jack, 1993-2004 (Box-folder 317: 4)
  - Holocaust, 1983-1990 (Box-folder 317: 5)
  - Holocaust Museum, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 317: 6)
    Correspondence related to an oral history. Includes notes from Joan Ringelbaum interview
  - Humanitas, 1979-1990 (Box-folder 317: 7)
  - Indian Law Resource Center, 1989 (Box-folder 317: 8)
  - Japan and assorted photographs, 1961-1994 (Box-folder 318: 1)
    Includes photograph of GS in Japan and of Joan Baez in Alabama in 1965
  - Jefferson Awards, 1987 (Box-folder 318: 2)
    Includes slides of a Group 19 fundraiser
  - Korea, circa 1976 (Box-folder 318: 3)
  - Kosovo, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 318: 4)
  - Lantos, Tom, 1986-1999 (Box-folder 318: 5)
  - Laos, poster, undated (Box-folder 318: 6)
  - Latin America, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 318: 7)
  - Letterhead, Aurora Foundation and Amnesty International, 1990s (Box-folder 318: 8)
  - Medical committee, 1975-1996 (Box-folder 318: 9)
  - Middle East, 1984-1995 (Box-folder 318: 10)
  - National Italian American Foundation, 1992-1997 (Box-folder 318: 11)
  - Nicaragua and El Salvador, 1984-1990 (Box-folder 318: 12)
  - Nightingale, Elena, 1988-1996 (Box-folder 318: 13)
  - Panzini, Tiberio, undated (Box-folder 318: 14)
    Reprints of translations of the 1945 letter
  - Physicians for Human Rights, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 318: 15)
  - Poems, 1974-2002 (Box-folder 318: 16)
    Includes poems written for GS and Joan Baez
  - Presidential Medal of Freedom, 1996-1999 (Box-folder 318: 17)
    Includes photographs from the event and brief correspondence with Clinton on human rights
  - Prigioni, Giulio (Consul General of Italy in San Francisco), 1996-1998 (Box-folder 319: 1)
  - Reagan, Ronald, 1978-1992 (Box-folder 319: 2)
  - Rohrabacher, Dana, 1984-1999 (Box-folder 319: 3)
  - Romaszewski, Zbigniew, acceptance speech, 1987 December 10 (Box-folder 319: 4)
  - Rostropovich, Mstislav, 1984-1986 (Box-folder 319: 5)
  - Russell, Madeleine, 1998-2004 (Box-folder 319: 6)
  - Sagan, Ginetta, 1973-2002
    - Articles by, 1973-1998 (Box-folder 319: 7)
    - Contributions to NGOs, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 319: 8)
    - Curricula vitae and chronologies, 1982-2000 (Box-folder 319: 9)
    - Friends, undated (Box-folder 319: 10)
    - Legacy, 1997-2002 (Box-folder 319: 11)
    - Letters to the editor, 1970-1996 (Box-folder 319: 12)
    - Material for speeches, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 319: 13)
    - Movie, 1986-1999 (Box-folder 319: 14)
      Includes film treatment of Sagan's life by Michael Rhodes
    - Obituaries, 2000-2004 (Box-folder 320: 1)
    - Pension, 1990-1991 (Box-folder 320: 2)
    - Press coverage, 1966-2000 (Box-folder 320: 3-7)
    - Researchers, 1978-1999 (Box-folder 321: 1)
      Includes outlines and research on Sagan's life
    - Vital records, 1952-2000 (Box-folder 321: 2-3)
  - Sagan, Leonard, 1975-1998 (Box-folder 321: 4-6 ,322: 1)
  - South Africa, 1985-1990 (Box-folder 322: 2-3)
  - Stanford commencement, 1996 (Box-folder 322: 4)
  - Stanford Institute for Research on Women and Gender, 1986-1995 (Box-folder 322: 5)
  - State Department, 1996-1997 (Box-folder 322: 6)
  - Styron, Rose, 1980s (Box-folder 322: 7)
    Includes photograph with GS signed by Joan Baez
  - Terrorism, 1988, 1995 (Box-folder 322: 8)
  - Tibet, 1989 (Box-folder 322: 9)
    Eyewitness accounts of demonstrations
  - Universal Declaration of Human Rights, 1998 (Box-folder 322: 10)
  - USSR, 1981-1989 (Box-folder 322: 11)
  - Verdeaux, Georges, and Jacqueline, 1971-2002 (Box-folder 322: 12)
    Includes notes by Sim Smiley from an interview with Jacqueline Verdeaux
  - Yugoslavia, 1995 (Box-folder 322: 13)
  - Woodward, Bob, 1988 October 16 (Box-folder 322: 14)
- Printed matter, 1971-2004
  - AFL-CIO, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 323: 1)
  - Africa, 1985-1990 (Box-folder 323: 2)
  - Americas Watch, 1989-1996 (Box-folder 323: 3)
  - Article 19 Bulletin, 1987-1989 (Box-folder 323: 4)
  - China, 1995 (Box-folder 323: 5)
  - Council of Europe, 1970 (Box-folder 323: 6-7)
  - Cuba, 1996 (Box-folder 323: 8)
  - Eastern Europe, 1989-1991 (Box-folder 323: 9)
  - Freedom House, 1985-1988 (Box-folder 323: 10)
  - Fromm Institute, 1990-1991 (Box-folder 323: 11)
  - Glasnost, 1988-1990 (Box-folder 323: 12)
  - Helsinki Watch, 1984 (Box-folder 324: 1)
  - Hoover Institution publications, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 324: 2)
  - Index on Censorship, 1979-1988 (Box-folder 324: 3)
  - International League for Human Rights, 1985 (Box-folder 324: 4)
  - Latin America, 1981-1992 (Box-folder 325: 1)
  - Lawyers Committee for Human Rights, 1986-1991 (Box-folder 325: 2)
  - Miscellaneous materials on human rights, 1979-1991 (Box-folder 325: 3-6)
  - Netherlands Institute on Human Rights, 1985-1990 (Box-folder 326: 1)
  - New Republic, 1986-1988 (Box-folder 326: 2)
  - News from France, 1998 (Box-folder 326: 3)
  - Refugees, 1981-1990 (Box-folder 326: 4)
  - Southeast Asia, 1989-1995 (Box-folder 326: 5)
  - State Department, 1987-1995 (Box-folder 326: 6)
  - Torture, 1979-1995 (Box-folder 326: 7-8)
  - U.S. Committee for Refugees, 1988-1990 (Box-folder 327: 1-2)
  - Women's rights, 1986-1995 (Box-folder 327: 3-5)
- Amnesty International, 1973-2003
  - Board of Directors list, 1996 (Box-folder 328: 1)
  - History, 2003 (Box-folder 328: 2)
  - Annual reports, 1971-1975, 1996 (Box-folder 328: 3)
  - Western Region, 1991 (Box-folder 328: 4)
  - Human rights education, 1988 (Box-folder 328: 5)
  - Internal documents, 1987-1995 (Box-folder 328: 6-9)
  - Printed matter, 1973-1996 (Box-folder 328: 10)
  - Printed matter and clippings, 1973-1996 (Box-folder 329: 1-6)
- Aurora Foundation files, 1968-1999
  - Audit, 1987 (Box-folder 330: 1)
  - Board meeting minutes, 1983-1986, 1995 (Box-folder 330: 2-4)
  - Tax return, 1990 (Box-folder 330: 5)
  - Correspondence regarding tax exempt status, 1988-1992 (Box-folder 330: 6)
  - Routine correspondence and internal documents, 1991-1999 (Box-folder 330: 7-8)
  - Financial records, 1991-1993 (Box-folder 330: 9-10)
  - Projects and fundraising, 1993 (Box-folder 330: 11-14)
  - Human rights clippings and collected articles, 1986, 1991 (Box-folder 331: 1)
  - Donations, 1985 (Box-folder 331: 2)
  - Contributions and grants, 1985-1991, 1995 (Box-folder 331: 3)
  - Internal documents, 1990 (Box-folder 331: 4-5)
    Includes photographs of Zbigniew Romaszewski and a report on a human rights conference in Leningrad
  - Internal documents, 1991 (Box-folder 331: 6)
    Includes photograph of GS and Joan Baez at Amnesty event
  - Living Legacy Awards clippings and correspondence, 1992 (Box-folder 331: 7)
  - Personal correspondence, notes, and other materials, 1998-1991 (Box-folder 331: 8-11)
  - Address lists, 1980s (Box-folder 332: 1)
  - Board of Directors correspondence and memoranda, 1984-1993 (Box-folder 332: 2)
  - Vietnam and Poland correspondence, 1983-1990 (Box-folder 332: 3-4)
  - "Summary of Aurora Foundation Concerns in the Socialist Republic of Vietnam,", 1980s (Box-folder 332: 5)
  - Articles on Vietnam from the San Jose Mercury News, 1987 (Box-folder 332: 6)
  - Boat people in Hong Kong, 1989 (Box-folder 332: 7)
  - Press release on Vietnamese Buddhist monks, 1988 October 25 (Box-folder 332: 8)
  - Resolution of normalization of relations between Vietnam and the US, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 332: 9)
  - Zbigniew Romaszewski correspondence, 1989 December (Box-folder 332: 10)
  - Witness list for US House of Representatives hearing on Cambodia, 1980s (Box-folder 332: 11)
  - Research material on Vietnam, 1980s (Box-folder 332: 12)
  - Receipts and contributions, 1991 (Box-folder 332: 13)
  - Le Tremblement des hommes, by Paul Goma, 1979 (Box-folder 332: 14)
  - Baja, screenplay by Dana Rohrabacher, undated (Box-folder 332: 15)
  - Personal letters of gratitude, 1980s (Box-folder 332: 16)
  - Notes and material for trip reports, 1986 (Box-folder 333: 1)
  - Board list, Vietnam clippings, and notes, 1990, undated (Box-folder 333: 2)
  - Addresses and notes, undated (Box-folder 333: 3-4)
  - Notes and correspondence, 1980s (Box-folder 333: 5-6)
  - Correspondence regarding the Reader's Digest article, 1986 (Box-folder 333: 7)
  - Notes and notebooks, 1980s (Box-folder 333: 8-11)
  - Vietnam chronologies, 1968-1994 (Box-folder 334: 1-15)
  - Notes and Vietnam clippings, 1980s (Box-folder 334: 16)
  - The Reagan Administration's Human Rights Record in 1984, by Helsinki Watch, 1985 (Box-folder 334: 17)
  - Inner Companions, by Colman McCarthy, 1975 (Box-folder 334: 18)
    With inscription to Sagan by the author
  - Secrets: On the Ethics of Concealment and Revelation, by Sissela Bok, 1983 (Box-folder 334: 19)
  - Donors, 1988 (Box-folder 335: 1)
  - Correspondence, 1981-1999
    - 1981 (Box-folder 335: 2)
    - 1982 (Box-folder 335: 3)
    - 1983 (Box-folder 335: 4)
    - 1984 (Box-folder 335: 5)
    - 1985 (Box-folder 335: 6)
    - 1986 (Box-folder 335: 7)
    - 1987 (Box-folder 335: 8)
    - 1988 (Box-folder 335: 9)
    - 1989 (Box-folder 335: 10-11)
    - 1990 (Box-folder 335: 12-13)
      Includes photographs of GS at Sierra Nevada College
    - 1991 (Box-folder 335: 14)
    - 1992 (Box-folder 335: 15)
    - 1993 (Box-folder 335: 16)
    - 1995 (Box-folder 335: 17)
    - 1996 (Box-folder 335: 18)
    - 1997 (Box-folder 335: 19)
    - 1998 (Box-folder 335: 20)
    - 1999 (Box-folder 335: 21)
    - Undated (Box-folder 335: 22)
  - List of Board members, 1989 (Box-folder 335: 23)
  - Articles of incorporation, 1981 April 14 (Box-folder 336: 1)
  - Aurora budgets, 1981-1983 (Box-folder 336: 2-3)
  - Barbara Piasecka Johnson Foundation correspondence, 1987 (Box-folder 336: 4)
  - Budget summary, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 336: 5)
  - Board meeting, 1988 (Box-folder 336: 6)
  - Board minutes of action, 1981 (Box-folder 336: 7)
  - Board members, 1985-1989 (Box-folder 336: 8)
  - Grant proposal by GS, 1984 March 28 (Box-folder 336: 9)
  - IRS exemption letter, 1982 (Box-folder 336: 10)
  - IRS correspondence, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 336: 11-13)
  - Notice of availability for public inspection, 1983-1989 (Box-folder 336: 14)
  - Projects related to the promotion of foreign literature, early 1980s (Box-folder 336: 15)
  - Statement of purpose, 1980s (Box-folder 336: 16)
  - Statement by domestic non-profit corporation, 1987 (Box-folder 336: 17)
  - Financial records, 1981-1982, 1989 (Box-folder 336: 18-20)
  - Certificate of incorporation, 1981 April 17 (Box-folder 336: 21)
  - Copyright regulations, 1983 (Box-folder 336: 22)
  - Deposit agreement with Hoover Institution Archives, 1983 May 24 (Box-folder 336: 23)
  - Examples of Aurora's work, 1981 (Box-folder 336: 24)
  - MIA/POWs, 1989 (Box-folder 336: 25)
  - Notes by GS, 1990 (Box-folder 336: 26)
  - Routine correspondence, 1988-1990 (Box-folder 336: 27-31)
  - Timeline of Aurora Foundation and GS's life, circa 1999 (Box-folder 336: 32)
  - David Hettig correspondence, 1990 January 18 (Box-folder 337: 1)
  - Tax exempt status, 1981 (Box-folder 337: 2)
  - Correspondence and memoranda, mainly regarding the Vietnam report, 1988-1990 (Box-folder 337: 3)
  - GS letters sent, 1988 (Box-folder 337: 4)
  - Letter to legislators regarding Vietnam, circa 1987 (Box-folder 337: 5)
  - Financial report, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 337: 6)
  - Fundraising correspondence, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 337: 7)
  - IRS correspondence, 1982-1984 (Box-folder 337: 8)
  - Board meeting minutes, 1987 May 27 (Box-folder 337: 9)
  - In Search of Asylum: Vietnamese Boat People in Hong Kong, Indochina Resource Action Center, 1988 (Box-folder 337: 10)
- Amnesty International, 1981-2000
  - Grace Cathedral event, 1988 (Box-folder 337: 11)
  - Proposal for "Sing" project, 1980s (Box-folder 337: 12)
  - "Women in Prison" report, 1985 (Box-folder 337: 13)
  - Urgent Action-South America, 1988 (Box-folder 337: 14)
  - Human Rights Now! campaign correspondence, 1988 (Box-folder 337: 15-16)
  - Meeting with the International Rescue Committee on aid to Poland, 1988 June 13 (Box-folder 337: 17)
  - Correspondence and notes, 1981-1989 (Box-folder 337: 18)
  - Stephen Denney letters, 1986 (Box-folder 337: 19)
  - Association démocratique des Français de l'étranger (ADFE), San Francisco, 1990 (Box-folder 337: 20)
  - Draft correspondence and writings, 1987 (Box-folder 337: 21)
    Includes draft of letter to Barbara Piasecka Johnson
  - Routine correspondence
    - 1995 (Box-folder 337: 22)
    - 1996 (Box-folder 338: 1)
    - 1997 (Box-folder 338: 2)
    - 1998 (Box-folder 338: 3)
    - 1999 (Box-folder 338: 4)
    - 2000 (Box-folder 338: 5)
- Aurora Foundation, 1981-2002
  - Poland, 1981-2002
    - 1981-1986 (Box-folder 339: 1-2)